Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2016; 108492
  - Subseries III:C: General Files, 1969-2016; 108580
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1973; 109183 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1974; 109182 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter (I), 1975; 109181 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter (II), 1975; 109180 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1976; 109179 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1997; 109178 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1978; 109177 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1979-1993; 109176 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Brooklyn College: Productivity Study, 1981; 109175 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Budget Cuts, undated, 1973-1974, 1981; 109174 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Burks, David: Memorial Contributions, 1984-1985; 109173 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Calandra Institute, 1987; 109172 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Campbell, Claude: Retirement Dinner, 1986; 109171 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Campus Security, 1979-1980; 109170 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Biographical Note, 1985; 109169 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence, 1972-1977; 109168 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence, 1978; 109167 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence (I), 1979; 109166 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence (II), 1979; 109165 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Carey, Governor Hugh, 1974-1978; 109164 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Central Office Chapter, 1975-1990; 109163 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Chapters: General, undated, 1995-1997; 109162 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1973; 109161 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Chronological File, Dec 1973; 109160 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Chronological File, Jan 1974; 109159 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1974; 109158 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1977; 109157 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Chronological File, Mar 1977; 109156 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Chronological File, Apr 1977; 109155 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Chronological File, May 1977; 109154 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Chronological File, Jun 1977; 109153 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Chronological File, Jul 1977; 109152 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Chronological File, Aug 1977; 109151 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Chronological File, Sep 1977; 109150 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Chronological File, Oct 1977; 109149 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1977; 109148 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Chronological File, Dec 1977; 109147 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Chronological File, Jan 1978; 109146 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1978; 109145 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Chronological File, Mar 1978; 109144 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Chronological File, Apr 1978; 109143 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Chronological File (I), May 1978; 109142 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Chronological File (II), May 1978; 109141 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Chronological File, Jun 1978; 109140 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Chronological File, Aug 1978; 109139 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Chronological File, Sep 1978; 109138 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Chronological File (I), Oct 1978; 109137 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Chronological File (II), Oct 1978; 109136 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1978; 109135 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Chronological File, Dec 1978; 109134 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Chronological File, Jan 1979; 109133 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - City College: Center for Biomedical Education, 1972-1974; 109132 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - City College: Center for Worker Education, undated; 109131 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - City College: Faculty Senate, undated, 1972-1973; 109130 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - City College: History Department Firings, 1974-1975; 109129 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - City College: Review Committee, 1972-1974; 109128 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - City College: School of Engineering, 1972-1973; 109127 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - City College: Women's Studies, 1972-1974; 109126 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - City College Chapter, 1972; 109125 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - City College Chapter, 1973; 109124 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - City College Chapter, 1974-1977; 109123 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - City College Chapter, 1980-1990; 109122 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - City College Chapter, 1991-1992; 109121 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - City College Chapter, 1993-1997; 109120 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - City University of New York (CUNY) Academy for the Humanities and Sciences, 1981-1982; 109119 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - CUNY: AIDS Policy, 1985; 109118 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - CUNY: Board of Trustees, 1979-1981, 1989-1993; 109117 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1977-1981; 109116 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1982-1987; 109115 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1990-1991; 109114 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1992; 109113 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis, undated, 1974; 109112 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis (I), 1975; 109111 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis (II), 1975; 109110 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis (III), 1975; 109109 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis, 1976; 109108 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis Clippings, undated, 1973-1974; 109107 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis Clippings, 1975-1976; 109106 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1983; 109105 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1984; 109104 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1985; 109103 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1986-1987; 109102 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1989; 109101 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - CUNY: Chancellor, 1973; 109100 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - CUNY: Chancellor, 1993-1995; 109099 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - CUNY: Contract Administration, 1974; 109098 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - CUNY: Contract Administration Guideline, 1973; 109097 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - CUNY: Disadvantaged Students, 1977; 109096 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, undated; 109095 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1975; 109094 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1976-1978; 109093 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1979-1981; 109092 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate Minutes, 1972-1975; 109091 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate Minutes, 1976-1978; 109090 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate Minutes, 1979-1980; 109089 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - CUNY: Governance, 1978; 109088 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - CUNY: Howe & Associates Report, 1978; 109087 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - CUNY: Instructional Staff, undated, 1972-1976; 109086 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - CUNY: Legislative Action Council, 1981; 109085 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - CUNY: Management, 1972-1975; 109084 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - CUNY: Master Plan, 1976, 1980, 1983; 109083 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - CUNY: Mission, 1978-1979; 109082 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - CUNY: Organizations, 1986; 109081 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - CUNY: Restructuring Proposals, 1972; 109080 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - CUNY: Restructuring Proposals, 1976; 109079 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - CUNY: Restructuring Proposals - Clippings, 1976; 109078 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - CUNY/PSC Relations: General, 1972; 109077 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - CUNY/SUNY Merger, 1976; 109076 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - CUNY Support: Reception, 1973; 109075 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - CUNY: Vice-Chancellor's Office, 1974; 109074 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - CUNY Women's Coalition, undated, 1974-1977, 1980-1997; 109073 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Civil Rights Act: Title VII, undated, 1972-1980; 109072 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Civil Servant, 1985; 109071 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Clarion, 1972-1978; 109070 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Clarion, 1984-1989; 109069 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Clarion Committee, 1973-1994; 109068 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Clarion: Notes, undated; 109067 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Coalition Bargaining, undated, 1978; 109066 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, undated, 1972-1973; 109065 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1974; 109064 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1975; 109063 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1976-1981; 109062 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education (I), 1994; 109061 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education (II), undated; 109060 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: Kugler Papers, undated; 109059 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: National Center, 1975-1981, 1987-1990; 109058 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: Rabban Paper, 1994; 109057 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Collective Bargaining: SUNY Staff Survey, 1978; 109056 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - College Laboratory Technicians (CLT) Chapter, 1972-1974; 109055 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Council of Senior Citizens, Pension Committee, and Belle Zeller Scholarship Trust Fund Files, 1982-1993 (Box 233, Reel 1-10)
    - CLT Chapter, 1975-1976; 109054 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - CLT Chapter, 1977-1981, 1986; 109053 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - College of Staten Island Chapter, 1975-1977; 109052 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - College of Staten Island Chapter, 1978-1979; 109051 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - College of Staten Island Chapter, 1980-1988, 1994-1997; 109050 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University: Unions, 1985; 109049 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, 1974; 109048 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1972, 1975; 109047 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Committee against Racism, undated; 109046 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1980; 109045 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1981; 109044 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1986-1991; 109043 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Educational Policy, 1973; 109042 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Community Colleges, 1973-1974, 1979-1989; 109041 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) Program, 1975-1979; 109040 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Computerization, 1974, 1976-1977; 109039 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: General, 1978-1981; 109038 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Cook, Beverly: "First Woman in Political Science", 1983-1984; 109037 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Cooper, Sandi: "Who Rules Higher Education?", 1979; 109036 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: General, undated, 1973-1980; 109035 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: General, 1981-1982; 109034 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: General, 1983-1986, 1993; 109033 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Chapter Chairpersons, 1972-1985; 109032 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1976, 1980-1987; 109031 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Cost of Higher Education, undated; 109030 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Council of Municipal Retiree Organizations (COMRO), 1981; 109029 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Credit Union, 1980-1981, 1985-1989; 109028 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - D'Amico, Samuel, 1974-1976; 109027 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Defense Fund, 1972; 109026 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Deferral Payments, 1984-1987; 109025 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Delegate Assembly: Meetings, 1974-1978, 1981-1982; 109024 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Delegate Assembly: Meetings, 1984-1990; 109023 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - DeMelas, Anthony, 1973; 109022 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Department Representatives, 1973, 1975; 109021 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Discrimination: General, undated, 1972-1979; 109020 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Discrimination: against Women, undated, 1972-1980; 109019 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Discrimination: against Women, 1982-1985; 109018 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Discrimination: against Gays and Lesbians, 1979-1985; 109017 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Discrimination: against Persons With Disabilities, 1976-1981; 109016 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Discrimination: age Discrimination, undated, 1974-1980; 109015 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Discrimination: CUNY Report, 1972; 109014 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Discrimination Claims: Baruch College, 1973, 1975; 109013 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Discrimination Claims: Kingsborough Community College, 1975, 1977; 109012 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Discrimination Claims: Lehman College, 1975-1976; 109011 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Discrimination Claims: Pace College, 1972; 109010 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Discrimination Claims: Queens College, undated, 1977; 109009 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Discrimination Claims: Queensborough Community College, undated, 1977; 109008 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Discrimination Claims: Staten Island Community College, 1973-1976; 109007 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Dissidents (PSC), 1973; 109006 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Doctoral Students Council, 1984; 109005 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Due Process, undated, 1975, 1982; 109004 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Dues, undated, 1973-1974, 1979-1981; 109003 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Elections: NYC, 1977; 109002 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Elections: PSC, undated, 1973, 1975-1976; 109001 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Elections: PSC, 1980-1985; 109000 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, 1973-1974; 108999 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, undated; 108998 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, 1977; 108997 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, 1978-1989; 108996 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Elections Committee: Appeals, 1986; 108995 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Emergency Fact Sheet, 1977; 108994 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Enrollment, 1979; 108993 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Equal Pay, 1972-1976; 108992 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1975-1979; 108991 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Evaluation, 1972-1979; 108990 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Ethics in Education (Newsletter), 1981; 108989 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Executive Council: Meetings, 1973-1977, 1981-1982; 108988 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Executive Council: Meetings, 1984-1990; 108987 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Fact Finders Report I, 1973; 108986 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Fact Finders Report II, 1973; 108985 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Fact Finders Report III, 1973; 108984 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Fact Finders Report IV, 1973; 108983 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Fact Finders Report (BHE Exhibits 1-12A), 1972; 108982 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Fact Finders Report (BHE Exhibits 13-33) I, 1972; 108981 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Fact Finders Report (BHE Exhibits 13-33) II, 1972; 108980 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - Fact Finders Report: Index to BHE Exhibits, 1972-1973; 108979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Fact Finding Meeting (I), 1975; 108978 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Fact Finding Meeting (II), 1975; 108977 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Action, undated, 1976-1977; 108976 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Development, 1988; 108975 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Evaluation of Administration, 1975; 108974 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Referral Service, 1976-1977; 108973 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Protection Act, 1979-1980; 108972 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education, 1974, 1978; 108971 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education (I), 1979; 108970 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education (II), 1979; 108969 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education, 1980-1981; 108968 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee, 1976-1986; 108967 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Finances, 1976-1978, 1982, 1986; 108966 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Financial Reports, 1972-1975; 108965 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Financial Reports, 1976-1978; 108964 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Financial Reports, 1979-1983; 108963 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Financial Reports, 1984-1988; 108962 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Financial Reports, undated; 108961 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Financial Reports, 1996-1997; 108960 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Fiscal Crisis, 1973-1974; 108959 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Fiscal Crisis, 1975-1977; 108958 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Fiscal Crisis, 1978-1983, 1998; 108957 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings, undated, 1973-1974; 108956 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings, 1975; 108955 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (I), 1976; 108954 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (II), 1976; 108953 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (III), 1976; 108952 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (IV), 1976; 108951 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings, 1977; 108950 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Freshmen Skills Assessment, 1977, 1980; 108949 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Friends of CUNY, 1980, 1986; 108948 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Funding for Higher Education, undated, 1974; 108947 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Furlough, 1975-1976; 108946 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Goldberg, Bernie, 1978-1982; 108945 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Governance, undated, 1972-1975; 108944 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Governance, 1981; 108943 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Graduate Center: Administrative Council, 1972; 108942 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Graduate Center Chapter, 1972, 1975, 1980-1981; 108941 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Grant Proposals, 1977-1980; 108940 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Grayson, Gerald: Study on LC Contract Implementation, 1972-1973; 108939 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Grievance Counselor's Manual, undated, 1972; 108938 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Grievance: Figueroa, Ramon, 1972-1973; 108937 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Grievance: Hatchett, John, et. al., undated, 1972-1973; 108936 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Grievance: Koch, Marianne, undated, 1970-1975; 108935 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Grievance: Kropp, Neil, 1972-1974; 108934 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Grievance: Mavridis, Nina, 1973-1974; 108933 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Grievance: Szulman, Ana, 1973-1974; 108932 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Grievance Procedures, undated, 1974-1981; 108931 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Grievance Primer, 1981; 108930 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Grievances: General, undated, 1972; 108929 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Grievances: General, May 1905; 108928 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Grievances: General, undated; 108927 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Grievances: General, 1981-1989; 108926 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Grievances: Brooklyn College, 1972; 108925 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Grievances: Hunter College, 1973-1976; 108924 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Harrington, Michael, 1975-1989, 1988-1989; 108923 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Health & Safety, undated, 1980-1989; 108922 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Higher Education Act, 1980; 108921 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Higher Education Officers (HEO) Chapter, 1973-1979; 108920 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - HEO Chapter, 1987, 1994-1997; 108919 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Higher Education Political Action Committee, 1995; 108918 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Hispanic Labor Committee, 1989; 108917 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Hollander, Theodore: Paper on Enrollment Projections, 1974; 108916 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Hostos Community College, 1972-1974; 108915 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Hostos Community College, 1975-1981; 108914 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Hostos Community College, 1983-1987, 1994-1997; 108913 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - HRC Financial Planners, 1986-1988; 108912 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Human Relations Conferences, 1970-1977; 108911 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Human Rights Committee, 1975; 108910 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1972-1974; 108909 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1975; 108908 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1976; 108907 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1977-1978; 108906 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1979-1981; 108905 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1983-1989; 108904 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Hunter College Chapter, 1994-1997; 108903 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Hunter College Chapter: Minutes, 1981, 1983; 108902 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Hunter College: Douglas Bumby Case, 1984-1986; 108901 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Hyman, Seymour, 1975-1976; 108900 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Independent Commission on the Future of the State University, 1985; 108899 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Independent Unions in Higher Education (AFT), 1979; 108898 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Ireland, 1985; 108897 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Internal Revenue Service: Home Office Expenses, 1978-1981; 108896 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - International Committee: Meeting Minutes, 2002-2011 (Box 230)
    - International Committee: Meeting Minutes, 2011-2016 (Box 231)
    - International Committee: Events and Subject Files, 2001-2015 (Box 231, Box 232)
    - Interns, undated; 108895 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Israel, 1974-1975; 108894 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Italian-American Affairs, undated, 1972-1983; 108893 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Jeffries, Leonard, 1992; 108892 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Jobs and the University Conference, 1977-1978; 108891 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - John Jay College Chapter, 1972-1975; 108890 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - John Jay College Chapter, 1976-1982; 108889 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - John Jay College Chapter, 1985-1995; 108888 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Mildred, 1979-1982; 108887 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Keppel Commission, undated; 108886 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Kibbee, Robert, 1977-1982; 108885 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Kingsborough Community College Chapter, 1972-1975; 108884 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Kingsborough Community College Chapter, 1976-1979; 108883 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Kingsborough Community College Chapter, 1980-1988, 1992-1994; 108882 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Kolodny, Jules, 1984; 108881 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Kraus, Arthur J., 1970-1978; 108880 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Kugler, Israel: Articles, undated, 1974; 108879 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Kugler, Israel: Biographical, undated, 1978; 108878 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Kugler, Israel: Correspondence, undated, 1972-1976; 108877 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Kugler, Israel: Writings, undated, 1973; 108876 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Kugler Luncheon & Scholarship Award, 1980; 108875 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Labor Caucus, 1973; 108874 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Labor Day Parades, 1983; 108873 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Labor Education, 1979, 1986; 108872 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Labor Education and Advancement Program (LEAP), 1977; 108871 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Labor Movement: General, 1979; 108870 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Labor Studies, undated, 1973-1981; 108869 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - LaGuardia Community College Chapter, 1981-1988, 1995-1997; 108868 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Leadership Bulletin, 1972-1973; 108867 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Leadership Bulletin, 1974-1975; 108866 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Leadership Bulletin, 1976-1978; 108865 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Leadership Bulletin, 1979-1983; 108864 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Leadership Directory, 1980; 108863 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Leadership Training Conferences, 1974, 1978; 108862 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - League of Women Voters, 1979; 108861 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Legal Services, Pre-Paid, 1978-1979; 108860 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Legislative, undated, 1973-1975; 108859 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Legislative, 1976-1978; 108858 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Legislative, 1979-1981, 1986-1989; 108857 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Legislative Breakfast, 1977, 1979; 108856 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Legislative Bulletin, undated; 108855 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Legislative Bulletin, 1985-1987; 108854 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Legislative Committee, 1973-1981; 108853 (Box 61, Folder 39)